Here's my solution to PYTorchModel creation.
下面说说我是如何创建 PyTorch 模型的
This takes in a few of the parameters we're familiar
这些参数我们都熟悉
with including a rule and framework version.
包括角色和框架版本
Then I'm parsing in the entry point which is where my predict.py file is.
然后传入入口点 即 predict.py 文件所在的位置
Now, for your code,
对于你的代码
this will just be in the source directory,
这个是 source 目录
but for solution cases and using source_solution.
但是对于我的解答代码来说 这个是 source_solution 目录
The main thing to note here is I'm parsing in
主要需要注意的是
some trained model data which is
我传入了一些训练过的模型数据
our modeled data from our trained estimator that was fit above.
也就是在上面拟合的已训练 estimator 的模型数据
So this gives me a PYTorchModel that I can then deploy.
这样就获得了可以部署的 PyTorch 模型
That's what I'm doing in this next cell,
在下个单元格中部署该模型
calling.deploy and parsing in some details about my deployment instance,
调用 .deploy 并传入一些部署实例参数
this creates a predictor that I can then use to make predictions on some test data.
这样就创建了一个预测器 我可以使用它对测试数据进行预测
If we actually take a look at this predict.py file,
打开这个 predict.py 文件
I can see that it starts off looking the same as the train.py file,
可以看到 它的开头与 train.py 文件一样
lots of imports including an import for the model simple net.
有很多导入语句 包括导入 SimpleNet 模型
Then I ask code to load a trained model here,
然后要求加载训练过的模型
and it also has functions for the type of
然后还有关于输入数据
input data it can see and the type of output it produces.
和输出内容的函数
In this case, this Content_Type is actually going to be numpy data.
CONTENT_TYPE 将为 NumPy 数据
In the predict function at the bottom,
在底部的 predict 函数中
I'm assuming the input data is going to be of a numpy type,
我将假设输入数据是 NumPy 类型
then I'm turning it into a tensor that can be parsed to our simple net model.
然后将其变为能够传入 SimpleNet 模型的张量
Finally, I'm getting the result of applying our model to
最后获得将模型应用到数据上后的结果
that data which should be a predicted class score.
应该是一个预测类别分数
So back to this deployed predictor,
回到这个部署的预测器上
I should be able to apply this to some test data features and evaluate the model.
我可以将它部署到测试数据特征上并评估模型
In fact, I've provided an evaluate function here,
实际上 我在这里提供了一个 evaluate 函数
that's very similar to the function we used in the linear learner example.
它与我们在 LinearLearner 示例中使用的 evaluate 函数很相似
It takes in a deployed predictor and some test data,
它的参数包括部署的预测器和测试数据
and returns a lot of granular metrics.
并返回详细的指标信息
The main difference here is that our model actually returns
主要区别是模型返回的是 numpy 格式的数据
numpy formatted data is dictated by our predict file,
如 predict.py 文件所要求的那样
and so we don't need to do much processing of the data here.
所以不需要对数据进行太多的处理
I'm simply rounding the output class scores to a one or zero
只是将输出类别分数四舍五入到 1 或 0
predicted label and squeezing this to get rid of any empty dimensions.
表示预测标签 并压缩以删除任何空的维度
Then the code is the same as before.
然后代码和之前的一样
I'm comparing the test predictions to the true labels and calculating true positives,
将测试预测值与真实标签进行比较
false positives, true negatives, and false negatives,
并计算真正例 假正例 真负例和假负例
and some binary classification metrics,
以及二元分类指标
and I'll print them out here.
然后输出这些信息
Now, if I run this code on our predictor, here is what I get.
如果对预测器运行这些代码 结果是这样的
I get an accuracy of about 80 percent,
准确率约为 80%
which is pretty good for our noisy wiggly data.
对于这样的杂乱数据来说 结果很棒了
I'd encourage you to try to improve this model by either increasing
建议你改进此模型
the hidden dimension and adding complexity to the layers or training for a longer time.
方法包括增加隐藏维度以及使层级更复杂 或者训练更长时间
Then as always, when you're done with evaluation,
然后像之前一样 评估完毕后
you should delete your endpoints.
你应该删除端点
I'd also suggest going to your SageMaker console and cleaning up any models,
还建议转到 SageMaker 控制台
config files, and data that you no longer need, and that's it.
并清理不再需要的所有模型 配置文件和数据
You've learnt how to deploy a custom PYTorchModel.
搞定 你已经学习了如何部署自定义 PyTorch 模型
Being able to deploy a custom deep learning model of
能够部署你自己设计的自定义深度学习模型
your own design is a useful skill for a variety of tasks,
是很有用的技能 有助于完成各种任务
especially tests that evade traditional methods for classification.
尤其是传统的分类方法无法解决的任务
It's also useful for tasks where you want to employ
此外 如果你想部署 SageMaker 内置模型
a different framework than SageMaker's built-in models,
之外的其他框架 这些技能也很有用
basically, allowing for greater flexibility in problem-solving.
使你能够更灵活地解决问题
So I wanted to say great job getting this far.
太棒了
I think you're well equipped to start tackling problems of your own.
你完全可以解决你自己遇到的问题了